<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Siddhant Shaw</title><link>https://mianto.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Siddhant Shaw</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Siddhant Shaw |</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 22:03:46 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mianto.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Refactoring to State Pattern</title><link>https://mianto.github.io/posts/refactoring-to-state-pattern/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 22:03:46 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mianto.github.io/posts/refactoring-to-state-pattern/</guid><description>Refactoring is a process of changing a software in a way that doesn&amp;rsquo;t alter the external behaviour of code and yet improve its internal structure. In this post I am trying to explain how one of the bad code smell can be treated using State Patterns.</description></item><item><title>Iterator Pattern in trees</title><link>https://mianto.github.io/projects/iterator-pattern-in-tree/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mianto.github.io/projects/iterator-pattern-in-tree/</guid><description>Implementing the iterator pattern in Java</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://mianto.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mianto.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hey there !!
I am Software Engineer, currently working as Member of Technical Staff at Salesforce. I have 2 years of experience of working with software industry which has been amazing journey so far. I am learning about the Architecture, Design Principles, Refactoring and Testing in different quadrants in a fast pace work, where product delivery is time boxed.
I have worked with an start-up during my internship period, in which I have developed application to extract information from a hand written prescription.</description></item><item><title>Glasses</title><link>https://mianto.github.io/projects/glasses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mianto.github.io/projects/glasses/</guid><description>A web application to detect whether the user is wearing glasses or not. In this project, I have used resnet50 model and fine-tuned the model on the dataset made from scarping google-images. Also visualize the prediction of the model using saliency map technique.
Project is open for feedback and contribution at Github</description></item></channel></rss>